Baseball. Tennis.
棒球. 网球.
-Look at that. Football.     -Yeah.
-看那个. 橄榄球.      -Yeah.
American football.
美式橄榄球.
I couldn't agree with you more, Kevin.
我完全同意你, Kevin.
I think football is a violent, overrated sport.
我认为橄榄球是一项暴力的, 评价过高的运动.
Do you call that violent?
你把那个叫暴力?
With all that padding?
带着那么多垫肩和护膝?
You don't see padding in rugby.
你不会看见垫肩和护膝 在英式橄榄球.
Now take baseball: a game of skill, finesse, strategy.
Now 比如说棒球吧: 一项技巧,灵巧性,战略的运动.
I don't agree with you there, Dean.
在那点上我就不同意你了, Dean.
Let's face it.
让我们面对现实吧.
Baseball's just a dull version of cricket.
棒球不过是乏味版的板球.
What do you think?
你觉得呢?
I'm with you Kevin.
我同意你 Kevin.
Baseball is boring.
棒球是无聊的.
-Not as boring as soccer.  -what?!
-不过没有足球无聊.    –什么?!
Now that's boring.
Now 那个是很无聊.
I say, let them use their hands.
我说, 让他们用他们的双手吧.
You're both very unreasonable.
你们两个都非常不可理喻.
Kev, name one sport more boring than soccer.
Kev, 说出一个运动的名字 比足球还无聊的.
-Golf.  -What?
-高尔夫.  –什么?
He's got a point.
他说的有几分道理.
That's your opinion.
那是你的观点.
What's your opinion?
你的观点是什么呢?
Golf is very exciting.
高尔夫是非常令人兴奋的.